comcast.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Statement

## **The Comcast Services and Websites Covered by this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy applies to the website at [corporate.comcast.com](https://corporate.comcast.com/) and to other Comcast or Xfinity-branded websites that link to this Privacy Policy, including [www.xfinity.com](https://www.xfinity.com/) (the "Websites"). The privacy policy that applies to Comcast’s television, Internet, voice, and home security services is available at: [ www.xfinity.com/Corporate/Customers/Policies/CustomerPrivacy](https://www.xfinity.com/Corporate/Customers/Policies/CustomerPrivacy); the privacy policy for Xfinity web services, which includes [my.xfinity.com](https://my.xfinity.com/) and Xfinity mobile apps, is available at [my.xfinity.com/privacy](https://my.xfinity.com/privacy); and the privacy policy that applies to the Xfinity Mobile network and services is available at [www.xfinity.com/mobile/policies/privacy-policy](https://www.xfinity.com/mobile/policies/privacy-policy). 

## **The Categories of Data That Comcast Collects When You Use the Websites**

Comcast collects the following types of data from users of the Websites: (1) the data visitors and users voluntarily submit (such as through order forms to purchase products and services, or by providing an e-mail address or other contact information to receive newsletters and other information, for example); and (2) connection, activity, and usage data, which Comcast records when visitors and users navigate to and around the Websites. Some of this data is personal data that identifies a particular person like an e-mail address or telephone number. But most of this data is not personal and identifies connections and devices by, for example, Internet protocol addresses and cookies.

We collect data when: (1) you provide information to us, such as your e-mail address, so that we can send you press releases and newsletters; or (2) you use the Websites to learn more about services availability in your area, or to consider or make a purchase. The information we collect includes: your full name, e-mail address, street address, zip code, phone number, and payment card or other financial account data. When you are considering a purchase of some Comcast services, we may also ask you to provide your social security number in order to run a credit check or to complete a purchase.

## **How Comcast Uses the Data It Collects**

Comcast uses collected data, including personal data, to determine which products and services to offer to you and on what terms. This data also helps us to offer you more personalized features, complete the particular function of the Websites you are using, and tailor the Websites to your interests to make them more useful to you. We also use your personal data to fulfill your orders for products and services.

Whenever you provide personal data through the Websites, Comcast will use that personal data for: (1) the purposes we disclose on the website when Comcast asks you to submit the data (such as, for example, to process your purchase of a new subscription to Comcast’s services or to send you e-mail newsletters); or (2) to send you marketing communications, promotions, or other communications about Comcast’s products and services, and to serve you advertisements about Comcast’s products and services on the Websites and other websites and services, including on third party websites and services.

## **How Comcast Shares and Discloses Personal Data**

Comcast considers the personal data it collects on the Websites to be confidential. Comcast uses third parties to assist us in delivering the Websites to you, such as hosting, technical integration, marketing, analytics, customer service, and fraud protection providers. We may share portions of the information we collect with these third parties, to the extent necessary for them to provide these services. These companies are acting on Comcast's behalf and are required, by contract with Comcast, to keep this information confidential and are only authorized to use it for specific purposes.

To make the Websites more valuable to users, Comcast may offer some features in conjunction with other providers. For example, when you click on certain functions on the Websites, such as to log-in to a shareholder account, you may be re-directed to a website that is not operated by Comcast and may be subject to a privacy policy that is different than this one. Once you leave the Websites, any information you provide is governed by the privacy policies that appear on the website to which you have navigated. You should read those privacy policies to understand how those sites use your information.

Comcast may be required by law or legal process to disclose certain personal data to Comcast’s lawyers, to third parties in connection with litigation, or to law enforcement personnel. Comcast will disclose personal data in compliance with applicable laws. We may provide this information without your consent and without notice to you when we are required to do so in order to comply with a valid legal process such as a subpoena, court order, or search warrant.

As described in more detail below, Comcast may provide non-personal data to third parties that deliver ads on the Website to you on Comcast's behalf.  They may also deliver ads on the Website to you on behalf of other brands that partner with Comcast and who, like Comcast, use the Adobe Experience Cloud. You may opt-out of these uses of non-personal data as explained in the “Cookies and Site Analytics” section below. Comcast will not provide your personal data to these advertisers unless you provide any required consent for us to do so.

Comcast may also share the data it collects with our affiliates that offer other Xfinity and Comcast-branded products, services and applications to help us provide you with Comcast services, other cross-platform products and services, advertising, and promotional offers that may be of interest to you.

## **Cookies and Site Analytics**

Comcast and its service providers use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, scripts, and similar methods to collect information on the Websites. A cookie is a small file stored on your computer or device that is used by your browser or Adobe Flash Player, for example. Cookies enable Comcast to perform various functions on the Websites, such as to track the number of visitors to the Websites, analyze how well our Websites are performing, make sure the Websites are running properly, and to allow you to use the shopping cart when you order products and services. You can control most cookies and similar technologies through your browser by adjusting its privacy and security settings. However, if your web browser is configured to block or restrict cookies, you may still access the Websites, but some functionality on the Websites may not work properly.

We may also use software technology on this website called clear gifs or pixels (sometimes referred to as "web beacons") to help us collect data about user activity. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. By accessing the Websites and navigating through them, you consent to Comcast setting cookies and using beacons, tags, pixels and scripts created by Comcast and by third parties. 

We and our service providers may also use cookies to deliver relevant advertising to you when you visit other websites, including advertising based on the products and services you viewed on the Websites. Comcast, or service providers acting at Comcast's request, may use cookies to determine what type of ad to display to you on other digital properties. 

The Websites comply with the applicable rules of the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) and Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB) self-regulatory programs. If you are accessing the Websites from the United States, the DAA program permits you to opt out of receiving certain targeted advertising and device tracking from participating companies. Go to the Advertising page at <http://my.xfinity.com/adinformation/> and select the Ad Choices icon to make your opt out selections. If you are accessing the Websites from the European Union, go to [http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) to opt-out of receiving certain targeted advertising and device tracking from companies participating in the European advertising self-regulatory programs. Making opt-out selections by using the websites offered by these self-regulatory programs does not prevent you from being served with advertising.  You will continue to receive ads from third parties, but the ads will not be targeted to you based on cookies or other technologies being set on your computer. As a result, ads that you see may not be as relevant to you. 

We (and some of our partners who may advertise on the Websites) also use the Adobe Experience Cloud to personalize and improve the performance of our websites, apps, social networking pages, and marketing messages. If you do not wish for your information to be used as part of this program, you can opt-out at <https://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html>.

We may collect data when you access the Websites on a particular browser or device.  We then may connect this data to another computer or device that you are using to access the Websites in order to provide you with a consistent experience. 

Some of the Websites use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies or other tracking technologies to help us analyze how users interact with certain websites, compile reports on the websites’ activity, and provide other services related to websites activity and usage. The technologies used by Google may collect information such as your IP address, time of visit, whether you are a return visitor, and any referring website. The technologies used by Google Analytics do not gather information that personally identifies you. The information generated by Google Analytics will be transmitted to and stored by Google and will be subject to Google’s [privacy policies](https://policies.google.com/privacy). To learn more about Google’s partner services and to learn how to opt out of tracking of analytics by Google, click [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy/google-partners?hl=en).

## **Marketing, Advertising, and Promotions**

Sometimes Comcast offers different subscription plans in different areas of the country for our products and services. When you visit the Websites, we may use the IP address associated with your computer to determine your general geographic location so that we can show you offers for products and services available in your region. When you are interested in a specific product or service, we may also ask you to enter an address or zip code to determine exactly which offer, product, or service is available to you.

## **Do Not Track Disclosure**

The World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) established a process to develop a “Do Not Track” Standard. Comcast’s Websites do not currently respond to “Do Not Track” signals sent from browsers.

## **Choices You May Make About Collection, Use, and Sharing of Personal Data**

Some Comcast websites that link to this Privacy Policy may allow you to submit your e-mail address for the purpose of receiving newsletters from Comcast. Most e-mail newsletters that you receive will include an “unsubscribe” function that allows you to ask Comcast to stop sending the e-mail newsletters to you. In addition, you may choose to opt-in or opt-out of receiving promotional e-mails about Comcast’s products and services by going to the web page located at [www.comcast.com/preferences](http://www.comcast.com/preferences) and following the instructions there. You may also opt-out of receiving marketing or promotional postal mail from Comcast if you contact Comcast at 1-800-COMCAST and ask us to put your name on our “do not mail” list.

## **Security**

Comcast follows generally-accepted industry standards to protect the personal data submitted to Comcast, both during transmission and once Comcast receives it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is entirely secure.

As an additional security precaution, neither Comcast nor any of our authorized service providers will ask you for your Comcast password in an email, over the telephone, or in an online support forum or chat. Do not give your Comcast password to anyone in any of these places.

## **Changes to Personal Data**

If you have submitted personal data on Comcast’s investor information page at [www.cmcsa.com/alerts.cfm](http://www.cmcsa.com/alerts.cfm) to receive alerts and information, you may visit that page to update or edit your personal data.

## **Users Outside of the United States**

The Websites that link to this Privacy Policy are for users located in the United States. If you use the Websites from outside of the United States, then by providing any data to Comcast over the Websites or through another direct communication with Comcast, you understand and consent to the collection, use, processing, sharing, and disclosure of your personal data as described in this Privacy Policy. You also consent to the transfer of your personal data to the United States for this collection, use, processing, and disclosure. The European Commission has determined that the United States does not provide an adequate level of protection to personal data and it may not offer the same level of data protection as the country in which you reside, whether that country is in the European Economic Area or elsewhere outside of the United States.

## **Children**

Comcast does not knowingly collect personal data from anyone under the age of 13 through the Websites website, and the Websites are not directed to children under the age of 13. Children should always get permission from a parent or legal guardian before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and telephone numbers) over the Internet, to Comcast, or to anyone else.

## **Change of Ownership or Other Business Transition**

If Comcast enters into a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, or the sale of all or part of its assets, your personal data will likely be part of the assets transferred. We will notify you if this happens if we have a means to contact you and we are required to provide you with notice.

## **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Comcast reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. When we change it, we will make a copy of it available to you by posting it at [corporate.comcast.com](https://corporate.comcast.com/) and at [www.xfinity.com](http://www.xfinity.com/), or through other methods. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will make you aware of them where we post the updated policy and may also notify you by other reasonable methods that we select. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy that will result in a new use, disclosure, or permission of access to your personal data that we previously collected and stored, we will obtain any consent that may be required by law.

You understand and agree that if you use this website after the effective date of the updated Privacy Policy, Comcast considers your use as acceptance of it.

**Effective Date: July 31, 2018**
